{
    "mc" : [
        {
            "name" : "mc1",
            "question" : "Java Servlets acts as the  ____ from the web request or some applications on the server.",
            "choices" : [
                {
                    "a" : "a.) Top layer"
                },
                {
                    "b" : "b.) Middle layer"
                },
                {
                    "c" : "c.) Bottom layer"
                },
                {
                    "d" : "d.) All of the above"
                }
            ],
            "correctAnswer" : "b"
        },
        {
            "name" : "mc2",
            "question" : "This method may allow your servlet to close all the connections of your database.",
            "choices" : [
                {
                    "a" : "a.) init() method"
                },
                {
                    "b" : "b.) service() method"
                },
                {
                    "c" : "c.) destroy() method"
                },
                {
                    "d" : "d.) POST method"
                }
            ],
            "correctAnswer" : "c"
        },
        {
            "name" : "mc3",
            "question" : "This is a very good method for the information to pass to a backend program.",
            "choices" : [
                {
                    "a" : "a.) POST method"
                },
                {
                    "b" : "b.) GET method"
                },
                {
                    "c" : "c.) init() method"
                },
                {
                    "d" : "d.) service() method"
                }
            ],
            "correctAnswer" : "a"
        },
        {
            "name" : "mc4",
            "question" : "In reading a data form using servlet, this method returns multiple values.",
            "choices" : [
                {
                    "a" : "a.) getParameter()"
                },
                {
                    "b" : "b.) getParameterValues()"
                },
                {
                    "c" : "c.) getParameterNames()"
                },
                {
                    "d" : "d.) getParameterForms()"
                }
            ],
            "correctAnswer" : "b"
        },
        {
            "name" : "mc5",
            "question" : "This object will enable the servlet to have access to the request headers being sent to the server.",
            "choices" : [
                {
                    "a" : "a.) HTTPServletRequest"
                },
                {
                    "b" : "b.) HTTPServletResponse"
                },
                {
                    "c" : "c.) HTTPJavaServletRequest"
                },
                {
                    "d" : "d.) HTTPJavaServletResponse"
                }
            ],
            "correctAnswer" : "a"
        },
        {
            "name" : "mc6",
            "question" : "This object is used to enable access and control for server responses.",
            "choices" : [
                {
                    "a" : "a.) HTTPServletRequest"
                },
                {
                    "b" : "b.) HTTPServletResponse"
                },
                {
                    "c" : "c.) HTTPJavaServletRequest"
                },
                {
                    "d" : "d.) HTTPJavaServletResponse"
                }
            ],
            "correctAnswer" : "b"
        },
        {
            "name" : "mc7",
            "question" : "This will redirect you to another site using the ‘url’ parameter.",
            "choices" : [
                {
                    "a" : "a.) public void setStatus(int statusCode)"
                },
                {
                    "b" : "b.) public void sendError(int code, String message)"
                },
                {
                    "c" : "c.) public void sendError(String URL)"
                },
                {
                    "d" : "d.) public void sendRedirect(String url)"
                }
            ],
            "correctAnswer" : "d"
        },
        {
            "name" : "mc8",
            "question" : "What is the data type of javax.servlet.error.exception?",
            "choices" : [
                {
                    "a" : "a.) Int"
                },
                {
                    "b" : "b.) String"
                },
                {
                    "c" : "c.) Throwable"
                },
                {
                    "d" : "d.) Class"
                }
            ],
            "correctAnswer" : "c"
        },
        {
            "name" : "mc9",
            "question" : "These are small text files stored in a computer’s non-volatile storage for tracking information.",
            "choices" : [
                {
                    "a" : "a.) Biscuits"
                },
                {
                    "b" : "b.) Cookies"
                },
                {
                    "c" : "c.) Candies"
                },
                {
                    "d" : "d.) Cakes"
                }
            ],
            "correctAnswer" : "b"
        },
        {
            "name" : "mc10",
            "question" : "This attribute gives data exact error message which can be stored and analyzed after storing in a java.lang.",
            "choices" : [
                {
                    "a" : "a.) javax.servlet.error.status_code"
                },
                {
                    "b" : "b.) javax.servlet.error.exception_type"
                },
                {
                    "c" : "c.) javax.servlet.error.message"
                },
                {
                    "d" : "d.) javax.servlet.error.request_uri"
                }
            ],
            "correctAnswer" : "c"
        }
    ],

    "tf" : [
        {
            "name" : "tf1",
            "question" : "Java Servlets are programs that can be run on the Web Server or Application Server. ",
            "choices" : [
                {
                    "a" : "True"
                },
                {
                    "b" : "False"
                }
            ],
            "correctAnswer" : "a"
        },
        {
            "name" : "tf2",
            "question" : "Java Servlets can be compiled using javac.",
            "choices" : [
                {
                    "a" : "True"
                },
                {
                    "b" : "False"
                }
            ],
            "correctAnswer" : "a"
        },
        {
            "name" : "tf3",
            "question" : "In the Java servlet life cycle, the init() method could be called many times. ",
            "choices" : [
                {
                    "a" : "True"
                },
                {
                    "b" : "False"
                }
            ],
            "correctAnswer" : "b"
        },
        {
            "name" : "tf4",
            "question" : "The destroy() method will be only called once at the beginning of the servlet.",
            "choices" : [
                {
                    "a" : "True"
                },
                {
                    "b" : "False"
                }
            ],
            "correctAnswer" : "b"
        },{
            "name" : "tf5",
            "question" : "The HTTPRequest object will enable the servlet to have access to the request headers being sent to the server.",
            "choices" : [
                {
                    "a" : "True"
                },
                {
                    "b" : "False"
                }
            ],
            "correctAnswer" : "b"
        },
        {
            "name" : "tf6",
            "question" : "To enable access and control for server responses, the HTTPServletResponse object is used.",
            "choices" : [
                {
                    "a" : "True"
                },
                {
                    "b" : "False"
                }
            ],
            "correctAnswer" : "a"
        },
        {
            "name" : "tf7",
            "question" : "The java servlet can access the functionalities of HTTP codes using the HTTPServletResponse object.",
            "choices" : [
                {
                    "a" : "True"
                },
                {
                    "b" : "False"
                }
            ],
            "correctAnswer" : "a"
        },
        {
            "name" : "tf8",
            "question" : "Filters are tools that the java servlet uses to screen out the requests sent by the client and the responses sent by the server.",
            "choices" : [
                {
                    "a" : "True"
                },
                {
                    "b" : "False"
                }
            ],
            "correctAnswer" : "a"
        },
        {
            "name" : "tf9",
            "question" : "Cookies are small text files stored in a computer’s volatile storage for tracking information.",
            "choices" : [
                {
                    "a" : "True"
                },
                {
                    "b" : "False"
                }
            ],
            "correctAnswer" : "b"
        },
        {
            "name" : "tf10",
            "question" : "Cookies can be used to track sessions by assigning unique Session IDs to each web client and for every requests from the client.",
            "choices" : [
                {
                    "a" : "True"
                },
                {
                    "b" : "False"
                }
            ],
            "correctAnswer" : "a"
        }
    ],

    "iden" : [
        {
            "name" : "iden1",
            "question" : "These programs acts as the mid layer from the web request or some applications on the server.",
            "correctAnswer" : "Java Servlets"
        },
        {
            "name" : "iden2",
            "question" : "In Java Servlets, this method handles the requests coming from the client and responses back to the client. <em>(please include the word 'method')</em>",
            "correctAnswer" : "service() method"
        },
        {
            "name" : "iden3",
            "question" : "In Java Servlets, this method sends the information of the user that was encoded which is appended to the request of the page. <em>(please include the word 'method')</em>",
            "correctAnswer" : "GET method"
        },
        {
            "name" : "iden4",
            "question" : "When a client would like to request resources from the server, request details are often stored into what?",
            "correctAnswer" : "Request headers"
        },
        {
            "name" : "iden5",
            "question" : "What object is used to enable access and control for server responses.",
            "correctAnswer" : "HTTPServletResponse"
        },
        {
            "name" : "iden6",
            "question" : "This file will be searched by the container when a Java Servlet throws an exception.",
            "correctAnswer" : "Web.xml"
        },
        {
            "name" : "iden7",
            "question" : "This is the data type of the request attribute, javax.servlet.error.status_code. ",
            "correctAnswer" : "Int"
        },
        {
            "name" : "iden8",
            "question" : "This attribute gives instruction about the exception raised, which can be stored and analyzed.",
            "correctAnswer" : "Javax.servlet.error.exception"
        },
        {
            "name" : "iden9",
            "question" : "These can be used to track sessions by assigning unique Session IDs to each web client and for every requests from the client.",
            "correctAnswer" : "Cookies"
        },
        {
            "name" : "iden10",
            "question" : "This driver is what you need to access the database.",
            "correctAnswer" : "JDBC driver"
        }
    ]
}